Guide to the Vassar College Photograph Files, approximately 1865-2014
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Vassar College Photograph Collection
approximately 1865-2014
Vassar College
40 cubic feet, 6 framed items
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Photographs of Vassar College events, programs, buildings, grounds, faculty, students, staff and administration.
Scope and Content Note
The collection contains photographs of Vassar College buildings; Vassar College views such as faculty gardens and houses, the farm, the golf course, Sunset Hill, Sunset Lake, Vassar Lake, and winter scenes; Vassar College alumnae, anniversaries, Class Days, departments, employees, ceremonies and events, dormitory scenes, student groups, athletics, classroom scenes, student dramatics, and wartime activities; other colleges; Eleanor Roosevelt and Vassar College; women in the armed services, suffrage activities, women's war work, child and female labor scenes, temperance crusade and other views of women; individual photographs of Vassar College faculty, trustees, and students; and miscellaneous subjects such as the 1925 eclipse of the sun, Lake Mohonk, Poughkeepsie scenes, and the 1938 World Youth Congress. Photographers include James E. Biddle, Christopher Gullmann, William Notman of Montreal, the Slee Brothers (George M., John N. and William P.), Alonzo H. Vail, and J. Watson Vail.
Related Materials
The college hired a number of local photographers for publicity work, including Margaret deM. Brown, the Vail Brothers, Warren Kay Vantine, Edmund L. Wolven and Chandler Photography. Collections of their photographs are also available. Contact the Archives and Special Collections Library for further information.
Access
This collection is open for research according to the
regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library
without any additional restrictions.
Subject Headings
Names:
Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962; Biddle, James; Gullmann, Christopher; Notman, William; Slee, George M.; Slee, John N.; Slee, William P.; Vail, Alonzo H.; Vail, J. Watson
Organizations:
Vassar College--Athletics; Vassar College--Employees; Vassar College--Faculty; Vassar College--Students; Vassar College--Alumni and alumnae; Vassar College--Buildings; Vassar College--Anniversaries, etc.; Vassar College. Board of Trustees; Vassar College--Description--Views; Vassar College. Class Day; World Youth Congress (1938)
Subjects:
Children--Employment; Eclipses, Solar--1925; Temperance; War--Women's work; Women--Education; Women--Employment; Women--Suffrage; Women and the military; Women college teachers--New York(State)--Poughkeepsie; Women's colleges--New York (State)--Poughkeepsie; World War, 1914-1918; World War, 1939-1945
Places:
Mohonk, Lake (N.Y.)--Description--Views; Poughkeepsie (N.Y.)--Description--Views; United States--Armed Forces--Women
Document Types:
Drawings (visual works); Photographs
VCL Categories:
Vassar College Audiovisuals and Realia
Encoding Information
Encoded by Laura Streett, March 2008. Updated by Emma Gronbeck, March 2023.
Acquisition Information
An artificial collection, collected by various departments of the Library over a number of years.
Other Formats
Some images are available digitally.
Container List
- Arlington (Folder 1.1)
- Care (Folder 1.2)
- Cider Mill (Folder 1.3)
- The Dutch Cabin (Folder 1.4)
- Hudson Valley Archeological Survey (Folder 1.6)
- Lake Mohonk (Folder 1.7)
- League of Nations, etc. (Folder 1.8)
- Poughkeepsie (Folder 1.9)
- Poughkeepsie. Montage from Collection of Henry Reichert (OV3.121)
- Poughkeepsie. Cottage Hill Seminary (OV3.132)
- Roosevelt, Eleanor (and Vassar) (Folder 1.10)
- Silver Bay (Folder 1.11)
- Silver Bay (OV2.001)
- Solar Eclipse, 1924 January 24 (Folder 1.5)
- Solar Eclipse, 1924 January 24 (OV1.001)
- "S.S. Vassar Victory" (Folder 1.12)
- Vassar Bank (Folder 1.13)
- Vassar Family. Lydia Booth (OV3.133)
- V. C. Administration (Groups) (Folder 1.14)
- V. C. Admission, Office of (Folder 1.15)
- V. C. Alumnae & Alumni of V. C. (AAVC). 1970- (Folder 1.16)
- V. C. Anniversaries. 50th (Folder 1.17)
- V. C. Anniversaries. 50th. Pageant of Athena [See also: V. C. Students. Dramatics, Pageant of Athena] (Folder 1.18)
- V. C. Anniversaries. 75th (Folders 1.19-1.20)
- V. C. Anniversaries. 100th. General (Folder 1.21)
- V. C. Anniversaries. 100th. General (OV1.214)
- V. C. Anniversaries. 100th. General (OV3.118)
- V. C. Anniversaries. 100th. Convocation, 1961 October (Folder 1.22)
- V. C. Anniversaries. 100th. International Conference, 1961 March (Folder 1.23a)
- V. C. Anniversaries. 100th. Main Building Centennial Party, 1961 February (Folder 1.23b)
- V. C. Anniversaries. 100th. New York Windows (Folder 1.24)
- V. C. Anniversaries. 100th. Photographic Exhibition (Folders 1.25-1.26)
- V.C. Associate Alumnae. Emily Townsend, 1884 (OV1.205)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. 1912-1939 (Folder 1.27)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. 1912-1939 (OV3.115)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. 1940-1969 [See also: V. C. Alumnae & Alumni of V. C., 1970-] (Folder 1.28)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Anniversaries. 50th. Lamp & the Bell, 1921 June (Folder 1.29)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Anniversaries. 50th, 1911 February (OV3.003-OV3.004)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Branches. Poughkeepsie (Folder 1.30)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Branches. Poughkeepsie (OV1.002)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Distinguished Alumnae (Folder 1.31)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Reunions. Classes of 1867-1879 (Folder 1.32)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Reunions. Class of 1880 (OV1.003)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Reunions. Classes of 1880-1889 (Folder 1.33)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Reunions. Class of 1884 (OV2.002)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Reunions. Class of 1887 (OV3.013)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Reunions. Classes of 1890-1899 (Folder 1.34)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Reunions. Classes of 1900-1910 (Folder 1.35)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Reunions. Classes of 1911-1915 (Folder 1.36)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Reunions. Classes of 1916-1959 (Folder 1.37a)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Reunions. Class of 1986, five-year reunion, 1991 (Folder 1.37b)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Reunions. General through 2007 (Folder 1.38)
- V. C. Associate Alumnae. Salary Endowment Fund, 1918-1922 (Folder 1.39)
- V. C. Baccalaureate (Folder 1.40)
- V. C. Baroque Colloquium (Folder 1.41)
- V. C. Buildings. Barrett Woodcut Proofs (Folder 1.42)
- V. C. Buildings. (2 or more on inseparable sheets) (Folder 1.43)
- V. C. Buildings. Proposed (Folder 1.44)
- V. C. Buildings. Alumnae House. Exteriors (Folder 1.45)
- V. C. Buildings. Alumnae House. Exteriors (OV1.004)
- V. C. Buildings. Alumnae House. Exteriors (OV2.003)
- V. C. Buildings. Alumnae House. Interiors (Folder 1.46)
- V. C. Buildings. Alumnae House. Interiors (OV1.005)
- V. C. Buildings. Art Gallery in Main (Folder 2.1)
- V. C. Buildings. Art Gallery in Main (OV2.004)
- V. C. Buildings. Art Gallery in Museum (Avery). 1875-1915 (Folders 2.2-2.3)
- V. C. Buildings. Art Gallery in Museum (Avery). 1875-1915 (OV1.006)
- V. C. Buildings. Art Gallery in Museum (Avery). 1875-1915 (OV2.005)
- V. C. Buildings. Art Gallery (Taylor). 1915 - (Folder 2.4)
- V. C. Buildings. Assembly Hall. 1916-1931. (Later Avery Hall) Exteriors and Interiors (Folder 2.5)
- V. C. Buildings. Assembly Hall. 1916-1931. (Later Avery Hall) Exteriors and Interiors (OV1.007)
- V. C. Buildings. Assembly Hall. 1916-1931. (Later Avery Hall) Exteriors and Interiors (OV2.006)
- V. C. Buildings. Avery Hall. 1932 - (Folder 2.6)
- V. C. Buildings. Avery Hall. 1932 - (OV3.107)
- V. C. Buildings. Baldwin House (Folder 2.7)
- V. C. Buildings. Blodgett Hall (Folder 2.8)
- V. C. Buildings. Blodgett Hall (OV1.008)
- V. C. Buildings. Blodgett Hall (OV2.007)
- V. C. Buildings. Calisthenium and Riding Academy. 1866-1876 (Folder 2.9)
- V. C. Buildings. Calisthenium and Riding Academy. 1866-1876 (OV1.009)
- V. C. Buildings. Calisthenium and Riding Academy. 1866-1876. Society Hall (First Philalethean stage) (Folder 2.9a)
- V. C. Buildings. Chapel. Exteriors, General (Folders 2.10-2.11)
- V. C. Buildings. Chapel. Exteriors, General (OV1.010-OV1.011)
- V. C. Buildings. Chapel. Exteriors, General (OV2.117)
- V. C. Buildings. Chapel. Exteriors, General (OV3.125)
- V. C. Buildings. Chapel. Exteriors, Cloister, Winter (Folder 2.12)
- V. C. Buildings. Chapel. Exteriors, Panoramic View (OV3.089)
- V. C. Buildings. Chapel. Interiors (Folder 2.13)
- V. C. Buildings. Chapel. Interiors (OV1.012)
- V. C. Buildings. Chapel. Plans (OV2.118)
- V. C. Buildings. Chicago Hall (Folder 2.14)
- V. C. Buildings. Chicago Hall. Photograph poster, undated (Framed Storage 2.8)
- V. C. Buildings. Classical Museum (In Avery) (Folder 2.15)
- V. C. Buildings. College Center (Addition to Main; opened in 1975) (Folder 2.16)
- V. C. Buildings. Computer Center (Folder 2.17)
- V. C. Buildings. Conservatory (Folder 2.17a)
- V. C. Buildings. Conservatory (OV1.013)
- V. C. Buildings. Cushing (Folder 2.18)
- V. C. Buildings. Cushing (OV1.014)
- V. C. Buildings. Davison (Folder 2.18a)
- V. C. Buildings. Davison (OV1.015)
- V. C. Buildings. Dean's House (Folder 2.19)
- V. C. Buildings. Dining Hall, Central (Former Students Building) (Folder 2.20)
- V. C. Buildings. Ely. 1933 - (Folder 2.21)
- V. C. Buildings. Ely. 1933 - (OV1.016)
- V. C. Buildings. Ferry (Folder 2.22)
- V. C. Buildings. Ferry (OV1.017)
- V. C. Buildings. Ferry (OV2.008)
- V. C. Buildings. Ferry (OV3.145)
- V. C. Buildings. Goodfellowship Club House (OV1.018)
- V. C. Buildings. Gymnasium, Alumnae. (Ely). Exterior. 1889-1933 (Folder 2.23)
- V. C. Buildings. Gymnasium, Alumnae. (Ely). Exterior. 1889-1933 (OV1.019)
- V. C. Buildings. Gymnasium, Alumnae. (Ely). Exterior. 1889-1933 (OV2.009)
- V. C. Buildings. Gymnasium, Alumnae. (Ely). Interior. 1889-1933 (Folder 2.24)
- V. C. Buildings. Gymnasium, Alumnae. (Ely). Interior. 1889-1933 (OV1.020)
- V. C. Buildings. Gymnasium, Alumnae. (Ely). Interior. 1889-1933 (OV2.010)
- V. C. Buildings. Ice House and Barn (Folder 2.25)
- [EMPTY] (Folder 2.26)
- V. C. Buildings. Jewett (Folder 2.27)
- V. C. Buildings. Jewett (OV1.021)
- V. C. Buildings. Josselyn (Folder 2.28)
- V. C. Buildings. Josselyn (OV1.022)
- V. C. Buildings. Josselyn (OV2.011)
- V. C. Buildings. Kendrick Hall (Folder 2.29)
- V. C. Buildings. Kendrick Hall (OV1.212)
- V. C. Buildings. Kenyon (Folder 2.30)
- V. C. Buildings. Kenyon (OV1.023)
- V. C. Buildings. Kenyon (OV2.012)
- V. C. Buildings. Lathrop (Folder 2.31)
- V. C. Buildings. Laundry (Folder 2.32)
- V. C. Buildings. Library (for Art Library see: VC Buildings. Van Ingen) (Folder 2.33)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Annex, circa 2000 (Folder 2.34)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Exterior (Folders 2.35A-2.36)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Exterior (OV1.024)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Exterior (OV1.025)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Exterior (OV3.005-OV3.008)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Exterior (OV3.104)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Exterior, undated; [framed, black-and-white] (Framed Storage 2.7)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Exterior (exhibit compilation board) (OV3.106)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Exterior. Photographed by E. M. Drouilhat, undated; [framed] (Framed Storage 1.6)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Exterior. Photographed by [V. A. Boris?], [1957?]; [framed] (Framed Storage 1.3)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Exterior, Winter (Folders 2.37-2.38)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Interior (Folder 2.39)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Interior (OV1.026)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Interior (OV3.009-OV3.011)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Interior (OV3. 105)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Interior (exhibit compilation board) (OV3.106)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Interior (Before 1963) (Folders 2.40-2.41)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Interior. Window (Folder 2.42)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Interior. Window (OV2.124)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Ingram. 1997- (Folder 2.43)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Ingram Construction (exhibit compilation board) (OV3.106)
- V. C. Buildings. Library. Lockwood. 1976 - (Folder 2.44)
- V. C. Buildings. Lodge (i.e. Gatehouse). 1865-1913 (Folders 3.1-3.2)
- V. C. Buildings. Lodge (i.e. Gatehouse). 1865-1913 (OV1.027)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. Before 1893 (Engravings, drawings, etc. only) (Folder 3.3)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. Before 1893 (Engravings, drawings, etc. only) (OV1.028)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. Before 1893 (John A. Lowell & Co. engraving) (Folders 3.4-3.5)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. Before 1893. Back views (Folder 3.6)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. Before 1893. Back views (OV1.029)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. Before 1893. Back views (OV3.012)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. Before 1893. Back views (OV3.082)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. Before 1893. View from Vassar Lake (OV3.085)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. Before 1893. View from Vassar Lake (OV2.122)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. Original front entrance (Before 1893) (Folder 3.7)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. Original front entrance (Before 1893) (OV1.030)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. Original front entrance (Before 1893) (OV2.014)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. 1893-1960. Front views, N.W. views (Folder 3.8)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. 1893-1960. Front views (OV1.031-OV1.032)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. 1893-1960. Front views (OV2.015)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. 1893-1960 (Folders 3.10-3.11)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. 1893-1960 (OV1.033-OV1.034)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. 1893-1960 (OV2.016)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. 1893-1960. Views from Chapel side. (Folder 3.9)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. Front view. Panoramic, 1909 (OV3.088-OV3.089)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior. Front view. Panoramic, 1909; [framed reproduction] (Framed Storage 2.5)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior, 1960- (Folder 3.12)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Exterior, undated (OV3.124)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Fire, 1918 February 12 (Folder 3.13)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Chapel (Folder 3.14)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Chapel (OV1.035)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Cooperative Bookshop (Folder 3.15)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Corridors & Bulletin Boards (Folder 3.16)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Dining Room (Folder 3.17)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Dining Room (Before 1960) (OV1.036)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Dining Room (Before 1960) (OV2.017)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Entrance (Before 1960) (Folder 3.18)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Entrance (Before 1960) (OV2.018)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Grocery Store and College Store (Folder 3.19)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Kitchens (Folder 3.20)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Library & reading room (Folder 3.21)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Library & reading room (OV1.037)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Miscellaneous (Folder 3.22)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Miscellaneous (OV1.038)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Parlors (Folder 3.23)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Parlors (OV1.039)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Retreat (Folder 3.24)
- V. C. Buildings. Main. Interior. Post Office (Folder 3.25)
- V. C. Buildings. Metcalf House (Folder 3.26)
- V. C. Buildings. Metcalf House (OV1.040)
- V. C. Buildings. Museum. Exterior. 1875-1916 (later Avery) (Folder 3.27)
- V. C. Buildings. Museum. Interior. 1875-1916 (later Avery) (Folder 3.28)
- V. C. Buildings. New England Building (Folder 3.29)
- V. C. Buildings. New England Building (OV1.041)
- V. C. Buildings. Noyes (Folder 3.30)
- V. C. Buildings. Noyes (OV1.042)
- V. C. Buildings. Noyes [Matted by the Loeb in 2009] (Separate OV Box)
- V. C. Buildings. Nursery School (Folder 3.31)
- V. C. Buildings. Nursery School (OV1.043)
- V. C. Buildings. Observatory. Early (Folders 3.32-3.33)
- V. C. Buildings. Observatory. Early (OV1.044)
- V. C. Buildings. Observatory. Early (OV2.019)
- V. C. Buildings. Observatory. Exterior, more recent (Folder 3.34)
- V. C. Buildings. Observatory. Exterior, more recent (OV1.045)
- V. C. Buildings. Observatory. Exterior, more recent (OV2.020)
- V. C. Buildings. Observatory. Exterior, more recent (OV3.120)
- V. C. Buildings. Observatory. Interior (Folder 3.35)
- V. C. Buildings. Observatory. Interior (OV1.046)
- V. C. Buildings. Observatory. Interior (OV2.021)
- V. C. Buildings. Observatory. Halley's Comet (OV3.119)
- V. C. Buildings. Off Campus Houses (Folder 3.36)
- V. C. Buildings. Olmsted (Folder 3.37)
- V. C. Buildings. Palmer House (Folder 3.38)
- V. C. Buildings. Palmer House (OV1.047)
- V. C. Buildings. Philalethean Hall [See also: V. C. Gymnasium] (Folder 3.39)
- V. C. Buildings. Physics Laboratory (Sanders) (Folder 3.40)
- V. C. Buildings. Power House (Folder 3.41)
- V. C. Buildings. Power House (OV1.048)
- V. C. Buildings. Power House Theater (Folder 3.42)
- V. C. Buildings. Pratt House [See also: V. C. Buildings. Warden's House] (OV1.049)
- V. C. Buildings. President's House (Folder 3.43)
- V. C. Buildings. President's House (OV1.050)
- V. C. Buildings. President's House (OV2.022)
- V. C. Buildings. President's House (OV3.001)
- V. C. Buildings. President's House (OV3.089)
- V. C. Buildings. Raymond (Folder 3.44)
- V. C. Buildings. Raymond (OV1.051)
- V. C. Buildings. Raymond (OV2.023)
- V. C. Buildings. Rockefeller (Folders 3.45-3.46)
- V. C. Buildings. Rockefeller (OV1.052)
- V. C. Buildings. Rockefeller (OV2.024)
- V. C. Buildings. Sanders Chemistry (Folder 3.47)
- V. C. Buildings. Sanders Chemistry (OV1.053)
- V. C. Buildings. Sanders Chemistry (OV2.025)
- V. C. Buildings. Sanders (1908, 1909, etc.) (Folder 3.48)
- V. C. Buildings. Sanders Physics (OV1.054)
- V. C. Buildings. Skinner (Folder 3.49)
- V. C. Buildings. Skinner (OV1.055)
- V. C. Buildings. Skinner (OV3.002)
- V. C. Buildings. Strong (Folder 3.50)
- V. C. Buildings. Strong (OV1.056)
- V. C. Buildings. Strong (OV2.026)
- V. C. Buildings. Students. Exterior (also called All Campus Dining Center (ACDC)) [See also: V. C. Buildings. Dining Hall, Central] (Folder 3.51a)
- V. C. Buildings. Students. Interior (Folder 3.51b)
- V. C. Buildings. Students (OV1.057)
- V. C. Buildings. Students (OV2.027)
- V. C. Buildings. Swift Infirmary (Folder 3.52)
- V. C. Buildings. Swift Infirmary (OV1.058)
- V. C. Buildings. Taylor. Exterior (Folder 3.53)
- V. C. Buildings. Taylor. Exterior (OV1.059)
- V. C. Buildings. Taylor. Exterior (OV2.028)
- V. C. Buildings. Taylor. Interior (Folder 3.54)
- V. C. Buildings. Taylor. Gate. [See also: V. C. Views, Gates] (Folder 4.1)
- V. C. Buildings. Taylor. Gate. (OV1.060)
- V. C. Buildings. Terrace Houses, 1973 (Folder 4.2)
- V. C. Buildings. Town Houses (Folder 4.3)
- V. C. Buildings. Van Ingen (Folder 4.4)
- V. C. Buildings. Vassar Brothers Laboratory. Exterior (Folder 4.5)
- V. C. Buildings. Vassar Brothers Laboratory. Exterior (sketch) (OV1.213)
- V. C. Buildings. Vassar Brothers Laboratory. Interior (Folder 4.6)
- V. C. Buildings. Vassar Brothers Laboratory. Interior (OV1.061)
- V. C. Buildings. Vassar Brothers Laboratory. Interior (OV2.029)
- V. C. Buildings. Walker Field House. 1982- (Folder 4.7)
- V. C. Buildings. Warden's House (Folder 4.8)
- V. C. Buildings. Warden's House (OV1.062)
- V. C. Buildings. Williams (Folder 4.9)
- V. C. Buildings. Williams (OV1.063)
- V. C. Buildings. Williams (OV2.030)
- V. C. Capital Campaign, 1969-1972 (Folder 4.10)
- V. C. Chapel Services and Lectures (Folder 4.11)
- V. C. Class Day [See also: V. C. Daisy Chain], 1888-1900, undated (Folder 4.12)
- V. C. Class Day, 1901-1913 (Folder 4.13)
- V. C. Class Day, 1906 (OV1.210)
- V. C. Class Day, 1906 (OV2.031)
- V. C. Class Day, 1914-1920 (Folder 4.14)
- V. C. Class Day, 1916 (OV2.032)
- V. C. Class Day, 1920s (Folder 4.15)
- V. C. Class Day, 1930s (Folder 4.16)
- V. C. Class Day, 1940s (Folder 4.17)
- V. C. Class Day, 1950s (Folder 4.18)
- V. C. Class Day, undated (Folder 4.19)
- V. C. Class Trees. To 1920 (Folder 4.20)
- V. C. Class Trees. To 1920 (OV1.064)
- V. C. Class Trees. 1921 - (Folder 4.21)
- V. C. Class Trees. 1921 - (OV1.065-OV1.068)
- V. C. Combined Drive (Folder 4.22)
- V. C. Commencement, undated (Folder 4.23)
- V. C. Commencement, undated (OV1.211)
- V. C. Commencement, 1897, 1901-1908, 1910 (Folder 4.24A)
- V. C. Commencement, 1911-1919 (Folder 4.24B)
- V. C. Commencement, 1915 (OV3.092)
- V. C. Commencement, 1920-1952 (Folder 4.25)
- V. C. Commencement, 1929 (OV1.074)
- V. C. Commencement, 1953-1956 (Folder 4.26)
- V. C. Commencement, 1953 (OV1.075)
- V. C. Commencement, 1957-1962 (Folder 4.27)
- V. C. Commencement, 1961 (OV3.123)
- V. C. Commencement, 1963-1969 (Folder 4.28)
- V. C. Commencement, 1970-1973, 1975, 1981, circa 1982-1986 (Folder 5.1)
- V. C. Community Church (Folder 5.2)
- V. C. Conferences. American Culture, 1952 (Folder 5.3)
- V. C. Conferences. "Minnewaska,", 1968, 1970 (Folder 5.4)
- V. C. Conferences. Miscellaneous (Folder 5.5)
- V. C. Conferences. Religion. College Religious Association Sponsored, 1953 (Folder 5.6)
- V. C. Conferences. Religion Department Sponsored (Folders 5.7-5.8b)
- V. C. Conservation See also: Lake Mohonk, Field trips (Folder 5.9)
- V. C. Convocation (Folder 5.10)
- V. C. Daisy Chain, 1895-1909, undated (Folder 5.11)
- V. C. Daisy Chain, 1910-1919 (Folder 5.12)
- V. C. Daisy Chain, circa 1910 (OV3.086)
- V. C. Daisy Chain, circa 1910 (OV3.091)
- V. C. Daisy Chain, 1912 (OV3.087)
- V. C. Daisy Chain, 1913 (OV3.090)
- V. C. Daisy Chain, 1915 (OV3.014)
- V. C. Daisy Chain, 1915 (OV3.092)
- V. C. Daisy Chain, 1920-1930 (Folder 5.13)
- V. C. Daisy Chain, 1931-1939 (Folder 5.14)
- V. C. Daisy Chain, 1940-1949 (Folder 5.15)
- V. C. Daisy Chain, 1950-1959 (Folder 5.16)
- V. C. Daisy Chain, 1960-1969 (Folder 5.17)
- V. C. Daisy Chain, circa 1961 (OV3.122)
- V. C. Daisy Chain, 1970- (Folder 5.18)
- V. C. Dance Groups and Dancing (Non-social dancing) (Folders 5.19-5.20)
- V. C. Dance Groups and Dancing (Non-social dancing) (OV1.204)
- V. C. Departments. Africana Studies (OV1.075b)
- V. C. Departments. Art (Folders 5.21-5.22)
- V. C. Departments. Art (OV1.076)
- V. C. Departments. Astronomy (Folder 5.23)
- V. C. Departments. Biology (Folder 5.24)
- V. C. Departments. Chemistry (Folder 5.25)
- V. C. Departments. Chemistry (OV1.077)
- V. C. Departments. Child Study [See also: V. C. Nursery School (Children alone); V. C. Buildings. Nursery School] (Folders 5.26-5.27)
- V. C. Departments. Child Study (OV1.078)
- V. C. Departments. Drama (Folder 5.28)
- V. C. Departments. Economics (Folder 5.29)
- V. C. Departments. English (Folder 5.30)
- V. C. Departments. Geology and Geography (Folder 5.31)
- V. C. Departments. History (Folder 5.32)
- V. C. Departments. Languages (Folder 5.33)
- V. C. Departments. Miscellaneous (Folder 5.34)
- V. C. Departments. Music (Folder 5.35)
- V. C. Departments. Music (OV2.033)
- V. C. Departments. Philosophy & Religion (Folder 5.36)
- V. C. Departments. Physical Education (i.e., Body mechanics, testing, etc.) (Folder 5.37)
- V. C. Departments. Physics (Folder 5.38)
- V. C. Departments. Physics (OV1.079)
- V. C. Departments. Physiology (Folder 5.39)
- V. C. Departments. Plant Science (Folder 5.40)
- V. C. Departments. Political Science (Folder 5.41)
- V. C. Departments. "The River" course (Folder 5.42)
- V. C. Departments. Unidentified Class groups (Folder 5.43)
- V. C. Departments. Unidentified Class Groups (OV1.080)
- V. C. Departments. Zoology (Folder 5.44)
- V. C. Eighteenth Century Weekend, 1964 February (Folder 6.1)
- V. C. Eleanor Roosevelt Chair [See: V. C. Lecturers and Visitors]
- V. C. Employees (Folder 6.2a)
- V. C. Employees. Dining (Folder 6.2b)
- V. C. Employees. Mr. Flagler (OV1.081)
- V. C. Euthenics Institute (Folder 6.3)
- V. C. Exam Teas (Folder 6.4)
- V. C. Examinations (Folder 6.5)
- [EMPTY] (Folders 6.6-6.9)
- V. C. Experimental Theatre [See: Drama Department Collection]
- V. C. Faculty